（御坂(みさか)妹）
横風が強い
照準を３クリック左へ修正
"Crosswind is strong."
"Adjusting scope three clicks to the left."
ビル風… 三方向からの渦
照準を右に１クリック修正
"Wind due to buildings: swirling from three directions."
"Adjusting scope by one click to the right."
"Target codename, 'Accelerator'."
目標コード　アクセラレータ
～♪
#10 Misaka Mikoto
The Oneesama
Originally, make-up lessons during summer vacation are to take place during July.
（上条(かみじょう)）
本来 夏休みの
補習というのは―
７月に行われるもので
Fact is, mine were scheduled near the end of July.
実際 ７月下旬に
行われたらしい
But I, Kamijyo Touma, still have to deal with make-up-make-up lessons as of August 20th, today.
だが 俺 上条当麻(とうま)は ８月20日の
今になっても再補習を受けている
Apparently, it's because I skipped the make-up lessons.
どうも 補習をサボったかららしい
（上条）
ハァ…
The reason I use a vague term like "apparently" is because I lost my memories.
“らしい”という曖昧な表現なのは
俺が記憶喪失だからだ
７月28日以前の記憶がない
I lost all my memories prior to July 28th.
従って
身に覚えのないサボリのツケを―
In other words, right now, I feel like I have to "pay" out of nowhere for lessons I didn't skip myself.
何だか知らないうちに
支払わされている…
…というのが今の俺だ
ンッ… 2,000円
Two thousand yen...
Such misfortune.
不幸だ
（美琴(みこと)）
ちょろっと
ボケッと突っ立ってんじゃないわよ
Excuse me.
Don't just stand there.
買わないなら どくどく
Get out of the way if you're not buying.
Tokiwadai Middle School's uniform.
（上条）
常盤台(ときわだい)中学の制服… 誰だっけ？
Who is she?
And, what's with her?
…で 何だ？　こいつ
I-friggin'-have-
（美琴）
私には…
a proper name called Misaka Mikoto, damn it!
“御坂美琴”って名前があんのよ！
いいかげん覚えろ どバカ！
Learn it already, you moron!!!
So I do know her...
やっぱ 知り合いか
その自販機な
どうも お金をのみ込むっぽいぞ
That vending machine eats your money, you know?
（美琴）知ってるわよ
（上条）えっ？
Yeah, I do.
（美琴）裏技があんのよ
（関節の鳴る音）
I've got a cheating technique.
お金入れなくても
ジュースが出てくる裏技がね
A cheating technique that will make it spit out some juice without giving it any money.
裏技？
Cheating technique?
Chaser!!!
チクショウッ！
（蹴る音）
Shorts...
（上条）
短パン…
（美琴）
この自販機 ボロっちいから―
This vending machine is old, so the springs that hold the cans be loosened easily.
ジュース固定してるバネ
緩んでんのよね
Only problem is that you can't choose what's going to come out.
何が出てくるか選べないのが
難点だけど
And, what's wrong with you?
…て あんた どうしたの？
Do all the rich girls at Tokiwadai do these kind of things?
（上条）
常盤台のお嬢さまは
みんな こんなことやってんのか？
（美琴）
女子校なんて そんなもんよ
That's pretty much how girls' schools are.
女の子に対して 夢見んなよ
（缶の開く音）
Don't be fantasizing about girls, okay?
Maybe it's thanks to you girls doing this all the time that the vending machine is broken, eh?
てめえらが寄ってたかって
こんなことしてっから―
自販機が
壊れちまったんじゃねえのか？
（美琴）
ハァ～ッ…
なに怒ってんのよ？　別に
あんたに実害あるわけじゃない…
What are you getting all angry for?
It's not like we've done any direct harm to you.
ハッ… のまれた？
...It ate your money?
一体 いくら のみ込まれたわけ？
How much did it eat~?
T-Two thousand yen...
2,000円
Two thousand yen?!
（美琴）
2,000円！
ひょっとして二千円札？
Don't tell me you gave it a two thousand yen bill?
まだ絶滅してなかったんだ？
So, you didn't drop coins in separately!
そりゃ自販機だってバグるわよ
ハハハハッ…
Heck, I don't blame the vending machine for eating it then!
Anyway, let me get it back for you.
（美琴）じゃ 取り返してあげるわ
（上条）どうやって？
How?
Like this.
こうやって
Hmm, so many cans are coming out.
（美琴）
あれ？　いっぱい出てきた
A two thousand yen bill didn't come out,
二千円札 出てこなかったけど
間違いなく 2,000円分以上
出てきたから これでＯＫ？
but I'm sure it spit out more than two thousand yen's worth of cans,
so settle with this, okay?
…て なに思いきり逃げてんのよ！
Hey, why are you running for your life?!
Hey!!!
（美琴）
おい！
Today's Topic - Mizuho Institute, the pathology research institute which deals with muscular dystrophy announces its withdrawal from the business.
（美琴）ほら！
（上条）あっ…
Here.
（美琴）
愉快に現実逃避してないで
ジュース持ちなさいってば
Get out of your happy denial mode and carry these juice cans already.
These were yours to begin with, no?
もともと あんたの取り分でしょう
なんか これを受け取った瞬間に
It feels like the second I accept these, I'll rapidly evolve from bystander to accomplice, and that scares me.
傍観者から共犯者に
成長進化しそうで怖いんですが
…て あつっ！
Shit, it's hot!
（美琴）
あっ “ヤシの実サイダー”
飲まないんだったら もらうわよ
Oh, if you're not gonna drink that Yoshinomi cider, I'll take it.
なにビクビクしてんのよ？
What are you all nervous about?
You look like someone who ends up with stupid problems a lot because he thinks he's weak when he's really not.
何つうか ホントは強いくせに―
自分は弱いと思い込んで
バカを見てる感じ？
You are one that has defeated
the one and only Misaka Mikoto, you know?
あんたは
この御坂美琴を打ち負かしたのよ
（上条）えっ？
（美琴）ならば 最低限―
At least take up the minimum responsibilities of a victor or else I'll have problems, okay?
勝者としての責任ぐらいは
取ってもらわないと困るの
（上条）
打ち負かした？　俺が この子を？
Defeated?
Be proud you were able to defeat me,
Me? Defeat her?
In what sport? What game?
スポーツ？　ゲーム？
one of the seven Level 5 espers in this Academy City,
Whenever girls say the phrase "take responsibility",
“責任を取ってもらわないと
困る”という言葉を―
女の子が口にすると
何やら不穏な響きがあるのですが
to the level that I can say "Ah, I lost to this strong of a man".
there's always a terrible ring to it...
なに知恵熱 出してんのよ？
Why do you look like your wisdom teeth are hurting?
ほれ　いいから ジュースお飲み
Come on, just drink up, all right?
美琴先生じきじきの
プレゼントだなんて
If I say this is a present from Mikoto-sensei,
then underclassmen at my school faint on the spot.
ウチの後輩だったら
卒倒してるのよ
Faint?
卒倒だ？　少女漫画じゃあるまいし
This ain't a shoujo manga, okay?
フッ… 少女漫画程度なら
かわいらしいんだけどね
If it was just the level of shoujo manga,
then I'd call that cute.
私が 常盤台ん中で
何て呼ばれてるか知ってる？
Do you know what I'm called at Tokiwadai?
Oneesama?
（黒子(くろこ)）
お姉様？
まあ お姉様！　まあまあ お姉様！
Oh my gosh, Oneesama!
My, my, Oneesama!
補習なんて
似合わないマネしていると思ったら
Pretending that you went to make-up lessons...
このための口実だったんですのね
...when it was actually a pretext for this...
ね… 念のために聞くけど
“このため”って どのため？
Let me ask, just to be sure...
What is this "pretext" you speak of?
Is that not obvious?
決まっています　そこの殿方と
密会するためでしょう？
To have a rendezvous with the gentleman there.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
（黒子）
はじめまして
My name is Shirai Kuroko; I serve as Oneesama's herald.
私 お姉様の露払いをしている
白井(しらい)黒子といいますの
もし お姉様に
ちょっかいを出す気なら―
If you intend on "hitting on" Oneesama,
まず
私を通してからにしてくださいな
please check with me first.
You... think...
（美琴）
あんたは…
...this weirdo looks like my boyfriend?!
（美琴）
このヘンテコが
私の彼氏に見えんのか！
That's what I thought.
（黒子）ですわよね
（上条）ウワッ！
Of all people, my Oneesama wouldn't be so low.
私のお姉様に限って…
それでは くれぐれも―
Well then, please make sure you don't make any mistakes, okay, Oneesama?
過ちは犯さぬように
してくださいませ お姉様
KUROKO!!!
（美琴）黒子！
（スパーク音）
変なウワサ流したら
承知しないわよ！
Spread some weird rumor and I'll have your head, got that?!
Teleport...
テレポート？
"Oneesama."
（御坂妹）お姉様
（上条）またか！
Not another?!
増えてる… 御坂２号？
Another one of you...
Misaka no. 2!
妹です …と
ミサカは間髪入れずに答えました
"I am her 'sister'," said MISAKA immediately.
Sister?
（上条）
妹？　けど 御坂何とかで
一人称は“ミサカ”なの？
But your name should be Misaka something, yet you refer to yourself as Misaka, right?
Don't people usually use their first names?
そこは普通 名前のほうを
使うもんなんじゃねえのか？
家ん中で混乱するだろう
It'd be a big confusion within the family, right?
（御坂妹）
ミサカの名前は ミサカですが
…とミサカは即答します
"MISAKA's name is MISAKA," said MISAKA without delay.
（美琴）
あんた！　一体 どうして
こんな所でブラブラしてんのよ？
Why are you wasting your time here?!
"If you ask for why... I am here researching," said MISAKA with a clean answer.
（御坂妹）
どうしてかと問われれば研修中です
…とミサカは簡潔に答えます
（美琴）
あっ ああ… 研修
Ahh... researching...
Hey, Sister, come over here for a minute.
おい 妹
ちょろっと こっち来てみようか
いろいろ積もる話があるから
いろいろ
There's a lot of things we need to talk about... a lot...
いえ ミサカにもスケジュールは
ありますと ミサカは…
"No, MISAKA has her own schedule," said MISAKA-
（美琴）
いいから！
It's okay!
来なさい
Just come.
We'll be walking this way,
（美琴）
じゃ 私たちは こっちの道だから
you remember your own curfew, okay?
あんたも
寮の門限とか気にしなさいよ
複雑なご家庭なのかな？
A rather complicated family, I guess?
It's so hot...
（上条）
暑い… 冷たい…
It's so cold...
It's so heavy...
重い…
ハハハハッ… 危ない危ない
That was close, that was close.
W-Wait... a minute!
ちょっと待て… こら！
Damn it.
く… くそ　俺が何したって…
What the hell did I do to deserve-
You...
（上条）
お前…
さっき 妹連れて
どっか行かなかったっけ？
Didn't you take your sister away somewhere earlier?
Wait, she was wearing shorts earlier, wasn't she?
（上条）
あれ？
さっきは短パンだったはずじゃ…
（御坂妹）
必要ならば 手を貸しますが
"I can lend you a hand if you need it," says MISAKA as she lets out a sigh.
…とミサカは
ため息交じりに提案します
Oh, it's the sister.
なんだ 妹のほうか
お前 ホントに 美琴に似てるよな
You really are the spitting image of Mikoto, you know?
美琴ですか？
…とミサカは問い返します
"Mikoto?" as MISAKA asks back.
ああ　お姉様のことですか
"Ah, you mean, Oneesama."
What's with the hardcore military goggles?
（上条）
そのごっつい軍用ゴーグルは
何なの？
"MISAKA, unlike Oneesama, has no skill in tracking the flow of electrons and magnetic forces,"
ミサカは お姉様と異なり
電子線や磁力線の流れを
目で追うスキルがないので
"and that's why a device to visualize them is needed," explained MISAKA cordially.
それらを視覚化するデバイスが
必要なのです
…と
ミサカは懇切丁寧に説明しました
Ah...
But didn't your sister drag you away back there?
けど お前 さっき
姉貴に連れてかれなかったっけ？
"MISAKA came from that way," as she points to where.
ミサカは あちらから
来ただけですが …と指さします
ふ～ん…
"Where shall I carry these juice cans to?" asks MISAKA while busying her hands and filling them.
（御坂妹）
このジュースは
どこまで運べばよいのでしょうか
…とミサカは両手いっぱいに
ジュースを抱えて問いかけます
あっ いいよ
あとは俺１人で運べるし
It's okay, I can carry these myself.
"Where shall I carry these juice cans to?" MISAKA urges.
（御坂妹）
このジュースは
どこまで運べばよいのでしょうか
…とミサカは催促します
Like I said, it's okay, it's okay.
だ… だから いいって いいって
お前が運ぶ義理とかないし
There's no reason for you to carry them.
"Hurry up."
早くしなさい
Yes, ma'am.
はい…
Hey, Kamijyo Touma!
（舞夏(まいか)）
ウ～イ！　上条当麻！
エアコン壊れたから 泊まりに来た
My AC broke down, so I'm here for the night.
I'll be making noise with my brother tonight, so bear with us, sorry!
今晩は 兄貴ともども
騒がしくなるけど堪忍な
Tsuchimikado's here?
土御門(つちみかど) いるのか？
He's not.
（舞夏）
いな～い
どこ行ってんだか さっぱり
I have no idea where he is.
（上条）
こいつは 隣の部屋に住んでる
同級生 土御門の義理の妹 舞夏
She is Maika, the step sister of Tsuchimikado, a classmate who lives next door.
Apparently, she goes to a maid school.
メイド学校に通ってるらしい
Maid schools must be tough.
（上条）
メイド学校は大変だよな
夏休み ねえんだろう？
You guys have no summer vacation, right?
うん　“真のメイドさんに
休息は要らない”ってのが―
"A true maid needs no vacation" is our school's motto.
ウチの校訓だからな
時に上条当麻
By the way, Kamijyo Touma.
Are those the "spoils of war" from
a raffle drawing you have in your hands?
その両手に抱えた戦利品は
福引き大作戦？
No, these have been paid for properly.
ちゃんと実費だぞ
ちょっとばっか汚れな一品だけど
A bit dirty of a job, but if you'd like one, go ahead.
欲しいんなら １本やる
Then, I'll take this.
（舞夏）
じゃ これで
Before I go, a tip on how to hide a runaway girl in your home:
最後に
家出少女をかくまうコツ その１
Let the girl wander around in the city during the day...
都会なら
平時は外をブラブラさせておいて
夜になったら回収という
“餌付け法”が いちばん楽ちん
...and take her home at night;
this "feeding" strategy is the easiest.
How do you know?!
なんで知ってんだ？
That Sister generates too much noise inside.
あのシスター 部屋ん中で
ドタバタ騒ぎ過ぎだろう
そういう趣味があるのですか？
"Do you have that kind of hobby?"
asks MISAKA in a slightly serious tone.
…と
ミサカは少々 真剣に尋ねてみます
真剣になるな
Don't get serious.
（上条）
うん？　何やってんだ あいつら？
What are those two doing?
（上条）
おい どうしたんだ？
Hey, what's going on?
部屋の鍵でもなくして
閉め出されたのか？
Lost your keys and got locked out?
Ah, it's Touma.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あっ 当麻だ！　違うよ
No, it's-
…て なに！
当麻が また知らない人と
Hey, you're with a strange girl again?!
You...
こいつは…
Perhaps, that is his fate.
（姫神(ひめがみ)）
もはや
そういう星のもとに生まれたのかも
He raises flags with other people and goes down their story routes.
それはフラグを立てるように
さまざまなルートを構築していく
And, what are you two doing?
（上条）
…で お前ら 何やってるわけ？
スフィンクスがノミだらけだから
取ってあげてるの
Sphinx's got fleas all over him,
so we're getting them off of him.
（上条）
えっ？ …ていうことは 部屋ん中も
ノミだらけってことかい？
Eh? Does that mean the room is full of fleas, too?!
Damn, so that's the reason I've felt itchy all over recently!
くそ！
最近 体が かゆいと思ったら…
Don't worry, Touma.
大丈夫だよ 当麻
What's... that?
何ですか？　それは…
It's a herb called sage.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
セージっていう薬草だよ
Put some heat on this
and it'll smoke out the fleas on Sphinx.
これに火をつけて スフィンクスの
体の中にいるノミをいぶし出すの
Smoke out...
“いぶす”って…
猫の香草蒸しでも作る気か？
Are you trying to kill the cat or something?
Wait, Himegami!
待て 姫神
お前は お前で なに出してる？
What are you pulling out of your sleeves?
魔法のスプレーと答えるしか
A magical spray, that's the only thing I can say.
どうするの？　それ…
What are you going to do with that?
All you need to do is spray at the insect.
魔法のスプレーは
害虫に向けて噴きかけるだけ
That's just a normal insecticide no matter how you look at it!
（上条）
どう見ても ただの殺虫剤だろうが
そんなの直接
猫に噴きつける気か！
You plan to spray that directly on the cat?!
"Concerning the way to deal with the cat..."
その猫についての対処法ですが
"...in essence, you want to physically remove the fleas from the surface of the cat without using chemicals, correct?"
（御坂妹）
要は 薬物を使わずに―
猫の体表面から
ノミを落とせばよいのですね？
says MISAKA to confirm.
…とミサカは確認を取ります
Yeah, but... how are you going to do that?
そりゃ そうだけど どうやって？
"Like this," answers MISAKA immediately.
こうやって
…とミサカは即答します
"With a particular frequency,
only the insects are killed," reports MISAKA.
特定周波数により
害虫のみを殺害しました
…とミサカは報告します
"For fleas inside your room, it is best to use the fog-type insecticide," advises MISAKA.
室内のほうは
煙が出るタイプの殺虫剤を使えば
簡単に駆除できるかと思います
…とミサカは助言を与えておきます
O-Okay...
（御坂妹）
それでは 用が済みましたら
"Well then, if that is all..."
（小萌(こもえ)）
1992年に
アメリカで再制定された―
Regarding the mandatory requirement for the re-establishing of ESP card experimentation in the United States in 1992,
ＥＳＰカード実験の必須条件ですが
the material for the card was changed to ABS resin.
素材がＡＢＳ樹脂に変更されてます
This is a trick to handle the problem of being able to tell the type of card...
（小萌）
これは 表面につく指紋によって
カードの種類が分かってしまうと
いうトリックに対するもので…
...from the finger oil making up the fingerprints on the back of the card and...
Hey, are you listening, Kamijyo-chan?
…て 上条ちゃん
ちゃんと聞いてるんですか？
ウ～ン… 聞いてますけど
I am, but it's not like I can gain power from listening.
聞いたからって
力がつくわけでもないでしょう？
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
カミやん レベル０やからな
Kamiyan's a Level 0 after all.
What can't increase won't increase.
（土御門）
伸びないものは伸びないのにゃ
But, but, you can't stop improving something you could just because you think you have no power and give up.
でもでも 力がないからって
諦めてしまっては―
伸びるものも伸びないのです
No. 3 in the Academy City, Tokiwadai Middle School's
Misaka-san was really a Level 1,
学園都市の第３位
常盤台中学の御坂さんなんて
元はレベル１だったのに
頑張って 頑張って―
and she worked really, really hard to reach Level 5 now.
レベル５まで上り詰めたんですよ
No. 3? Her?
（上条）
第３位って… あれが？
うん？　上条ちゃん
御坂さんとお知り合い？
Kamijyo-chan, you know Misaka-san?
いや　別に
No, not really...
あっ オッス！
そっちも補習で 今 帰りってとこ？
Yo.
You headed home after make-up lessons, too?
ああ　あんたか
Oh, it's you.
I don't like that blimp very much.
（美琴）
私 あの飛行船って
嫌いなのよね
Why not?
（上条）
なんでだよ？
（美琴）
機械が決めた政策に
人間が従ってるからよ
Because humans are abiding by the policies set by machines.
（上条）
機械？
ああ 何だっけ？　えっと…
Machines?
Ah, what was it... umm...
"Tree Diagram" or something?
“樹形図の設計者(ツリーダイアグラム)”だっけか？
Tree Diagram - the most powerful supercomputer in the world, installed inside Orihime 1,
（美琴）
樹形図の設計者(ツリーダイアグラム)
気象データ解析という建て前で
学園都市が打ち上げた人工衛星
the artificial satellite the Academy City launched using "weather data processing" as a cover.
おりひめ１号に搭載された
世界最高のスーパーコンピューター
…なんていわれてるけど
That's what they say, but does something as extravagant as that really exist?
実際 そんなバカげた物が
存在するのかしらね
Huh?
（上条）
いった…
てめえ いきなり何すんだ！
Oww!
Why did you do that all of a sudden?!
Ahh, I've become a bit of a poet now!
ああ
ちょっと詩人になっちゃったわ
Huh?
（上条）はぁ？
（美琴）じゃ 私 こっちだから
I'm this way, bye.
That's Mikoto, right?
美琴 …だよな？
（上条）
妹のほうかよ
Oh, it's her sister.
Man, I really can't tell the difference without the goggles.
つうか ゴーグルなくなると
ホントに見分けがつかねえな
ウッス！　昨日は
ジュースとノミの件 サンキューな
Yo, thanks for the juice and fleas yesterday.
"Your compliments were not
my objectives," answers MISAKA.
感謝の言葉が目的ではありません
…とミサカは返答します
（上条）
なんだ　それ あげないのかよ？
What, you're not going to feed it that?
ミサカには この猫に
餌を与えることは不可能でしょう
"It is probably impossible for MISAKA to feed this to the cat," concludes MISAKA.
…と結論づけます
"MISAKA possesses a very critical defect," as MISAKA gives additional explanations.
ミサカには ひとつ
致命的な欠陥がありますから
（御坂妹）…と補足説明します
（上条）欠陥？
Defect?
（御坂妹）
ミサカの体は
常に微弱な磁場を形成します
"MISAKA's body passively generates
a weak magnetic field," explains MISAKA.
…とミサカは説明します
"Its magnitude isn't one a human body can detect, but that is not the case for other animals."
人体には感知できない程度ですが
ほかの動物だと異なるようです
（上条）
ふ～ん…
"At this rate, it is to fear that this cat will be taken away to an animal shelter," indicates MISAKA.
このままだと 保健所に
回収されるおそれがあります
…とミサカは指摘します
You're... right... but...
（上条）
そりゃ まあ そうだけど…
（御坂妹）
保健所に回収された動物が―
"Do you know how animals taken to
an animal shelter are treated?" presses MISAKA.
どのような扱いを受けるか
知っていますか？
…とミサカは問い詰めます
Hey, you picked it up, at least give it a name.
（上条）
お前が拾ったんだから
せめて名前ぐらい お前が付けろよ
"Dog."
（御坂妹）犬…
（上条）えっ？
"This black cat will be called 'Dog'," declares MISAKA.
この黒猫には“犬”
…とミサカは命名します
"A cat, yet 'Dog'... hehe..."
猫なのに“犬”
いや だから 真面目に…
もっと威厳のある名前をさ
No, let's be serious... let's give it one that's more majestic or something...
"Then, 'Tokugawa Ieyasu'," as MISAKA changes her mind.
では “徳川家康(とくがわ いえやす)”
…とミサカは再考します
That's too majestic, okay?!
威厳ありすぎだろう！
"Schrödinger, then."
（御坂妹）
ならば “シュレディンガー”と
（上条）
その名前は 猫にとって禁句だ
That name is taboo for cats.
（上条）
すぐ買ってくるから
ここで ちょろっと待っててくれ
I'll be out right away, so wait here for a bit.
"Do you want reference books for taking care of cats?" says MISAKA to get confirmation.
（御坂妹）
猫の飼育法に関する書籍が
欲しいのですか？
…とミサカは確認を取ります
（上条）
書籍というより 知識だな
More like knowledge and not the books themselves.
You saw them, too, right?
お前も見ただろう？
あの修道服と巫女(みこ)装束
The Sister clothing and the shrine maiden clothing.
念のために申し上げますが
"I would like to remind you, just in case,"
猫の命を不用意に扱った場合は
動物愛護法により 罪に問われます
"but mistreating the lives of cats is a crime under the Animal Protection Act," warns MISAKA.
…とミサカは警告します
What, are you angry?
えっ なに？　怒ってる？
"I am not angry."
怒ってはいません
"I am saying that just because you weren't directly involved in such mistreatment does not mean you are off the hook,"
あなたが直接 関わっていなければ
それでよいという話ではありません
…とミサカは注意を促します
advises MISAKA.
My bad...
（上条）
ごめん
うん？　そういや 猫を抱えたまま
店ん中に入っても大丈夫かな？
Oh, is it okay for me to bring a cat into a bookstore?
果てしなく
説明くさいセリフなのですが
"This may sound quite mundane, but please refrain from letting us take care of it, thank you," as MISAKA-
こちらに預けるのは
ご遠慮くださいとミサカは…
磁場の出る体質のおかげで
猫に嫌われてるって？
You said cats don't like you because of your magnetic field?
ならば その壁を乗り越えてこそ
真の友情が芽生えるってもんだろう
Then overcome that barrier, and true friendship is born.
"Gosh... with what kind of mentality can someone throw a cat like that?" utters MISAKA to herself.
まったく 一体 どんな神経で―
子猫を投げることを
よしとしたんでしょうか
…と ミサカは
ひとり つぶやきます
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
さ～て 問題です
Now, question.
Who comes to mind when they ask who the strongest Level 5 in this Academy City is?
学園都市最強のレベル５といえば
誰でしょうか？
～♪
Next Episode
Massacres that have taken place in the name of "experimentation".
（上条）
実験という名のもとに
繰り返される殺戮(さつりく)
Those targets are called "Sisters".
その対象は“妹達(シスターズ)”と呼ばれる
なあ 御坂
お前は どこまで知っているんだ？
Hey, MISAKA, how much do you know?
次回 「妹達(シスターズ)」
Next time, "Sisters".
When science and magic cross paths,
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
this epic will begin!